A quarter their numbers have come,
we have got the market reaction, this is a difficult
picture, if you subscribe to this company,
subscribe to this video,
subscribe to the channel, what do
we show you,
what do we show you from the revenue from the operations, if we
talk about last year then
9492, at this time when you
see clear things there, if you like this video,
then pressure nickel cotton fabric is cotton, it
comes to 3254, that is, you can see the
revenue from operation, subscribe here,
you can see in both of these, here you
subscribe, so here I have done all the
questions,
lights, all the things, after that
add on the total eclipse, talk about the total expense,
last three four plus point
for plants and this time Rajdhani Night Club,
this gram flour, then the company expenses have increased a little,
its lips are cotton and here you search a
little, subscribe here and secondly,
I should not do this here,
if you subscribe,
keep the alarm clock here, focus on it,
after paying the net profit after tax, this way it is in the last and after that
you see here  There will be improvement if we talk about
subscription, if you
subscribe from there then if you focus
on thank you, it will be a good
thing but let me show you
1531 mostly so we should follow something in this,
then not only in this, now secondly
this is just an excuse, see tomato
needs a trigger, the market
needs extra to go to open office, for the first
two-three days we should definitely see that item
girl was bullish, then those who came close, did
not come, it happened today, which is not
good, that is why profit booking has happened,
something like this has happened in the market, plus
it has its own Regent Park, and
we have seen the later result Amit, if you
try to understand it in time, the
most important company to understand in front of you is JP
Services, it provides these sectors,
if it is banking function
service interest, that too manufacturing,
energy and utility and hi-tech media
entertainment and after that it is written form,
in all these subscribe, do not understand anything that
if you subscribe to it,
and this time cigarette improve point,
here I have six  5551 from here
I can do this, I did not subscribe to this
and here you have to subscribe in front of all these,
click on search here,
it has done a very good job, just Quite
Amazing, show it to you and it is not very big,
its link profit, if we talk about last and this
time, then if we talk about there, if we
talk about gas here, but stay and to
understand, the quarterly
result operating profit is in front of you, subscribe,
chapter on profit means forces next
year Agroha 519 improvement, after that
do 545 that after that then you will get profit,
you have to subscribe to our channel till now
and here if you subscribe
to the
video product, then Jio 4G phone
is where this company has invested
in one of the quarters of Noida company,
it means this company is the best, the company
always stays with us, so it runs on subscription, so if we
talk there, then if you
want this, then subscribe, you can subscribe to this company till
now, but this A A
100 pattern should be shown to you, it will definitely be
stopping its basic, what does it tell  This is a WA
British police pattern,
let's understand here, this is a long term
appointment subscribe and this is that in the past few
days and after that also subscribe,
tried but you have not seen such volume here, since the
beginning, see, therefore it is an excellent
company, the results have come, there is confusion in this,
share whatever is there here and if
you do not need it, if we have
got the subscription, then if you will give here
averaging can be done because and
after that, see if there is a reversal in it
or not, then definitely subscribe
and subscribe from the other side,
subscribe here, this is why we will
show the next process, the
results have come, the correction has been cleared,
so after giving it, now you should go to school,
those who have
500 to 1000, there is no need to worry, you will know how to
return subscribe,
subscribe to the channel, you can like the video,
subscribe to the channel